Huynh Minh Tam

Software Engineer

A passionate software engineer with more than half year of hands-on experience as a FRONT-END developer. My expertise spans Javascript /TypeScript programming languages and extends to another programming languages . Always excited to tackle new challenges in the ever-evolving world of tech.

Work Experience

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam 0823532831 hunhminhtam@gmail.com

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Intern Frontend Developer

FPT software

• At FPT Software, I'm learning to design effective UX/UI, implementing interfaces from Figma, and developing modules like CRUD.

Mar 2024 - Jun 2024 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Frontend Developer

Cydeva technology

 At Cydeva technology. Skilled in developing and maintaining projects. Proficient in both front-end and back-end technologies, with expertise in Typescript/Javascipt programming languages and a bit mobile development.

Education

Dec 2020 - Dec 2024

FPT University

Software Engineering

Fourth-year student majoring in Software Engineering. Passionate about applying theoretical knowledge to real-world projects and continuously expanding my skills in software development.

Skills

Backend Frontend Other MySQL, Mongo DB JavaScipt /TypeScipt NextJS / ReactJS Java Redux/ Redux toolkit / Zustand RabbitMQ Node js express React Query /SWR Socket IO Github CI/CD Cloudinary **Projects** Apr 2024 - Present Hostie is my entrepreneurial project aimed at connecting brokers and property owners in the short-term accommodation sector. Utilizing thehostie.com technologies like Golang and Java, Hostie enhances communication and Hostie operational efficiency, demonstrating my capability to innovate and Fullstack developer integrate advanced solutions in hospitality management Jan 2023 - March 2023 School project .Experienced in Hella backend development, Hella external api development. Hella Booking **Backend Developer** My pet project based on https://tinhocngoisao.com/. Webapp is a small ecommerce platforms. Aug 2024 - Oct 2024 Pc store Fullstack developer **CERTIFICATIONS** CertNexus Certified Ethical Emerging Technologies Apr 2023 Jan 2023 Software Development Lifecycle Oct 2022 Web Design for Everybody Jun 2022 **Computer Communications DEC 2021** Toeic 610

SOCIAL NETWORK

Gitub: https://github.com/TamHM1410
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/toilatam1410/